[
  {
    "question": "Who smiles the most?",
    "answer": "... smiles the most"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who laughs at the strangest things?",
    "answer": "... laughs at the strangest things"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who makes the wierdest jokes?",
    "answer": "... makes the wierdest jokes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the biggest simp?",
    "answer": "... is the biggest simp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the cutest?",
    "answer": "... is the cutest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who gives the best advice?",
    "answer": "... gives the best advice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has the biggest heart?",
    "answer": "... has the biggest heart UwU"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the wisest?",
    "answer": "... is the wisest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who would you date?",
    "answer": "Everyone wants to date ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to embarrass themeselves on a date?",
    "answer": "... is probably going embarrass themselves on a date lol"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the smartest?",
    "answer": "... is the smartest!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who do you trust the most?",
    "answer": "We trust ... the most :)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the funniest",
    "answer": "... is the funniest!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Eats the most pizza?",
    "answer": "... eats the most pizza"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the biggest heartbreaker?",
    "answer": "The biggest heartbreaker is ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the photogenic?",
    "answer": "The photogenic is ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to become president?",
    "answer": "Most likely to become president is ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to get into a bar fight?",
    "answer": "Most likely to get into a bar fight is ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to become famous?",
    "answer": "... is most likely to become famous!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to be a supermodel?",
    "answer": "Most likely to be a supermodel is ..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to laugh at a wrong moment?",
    "answer": "... is most likely to laugh at the wrong moment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is going to get married first?",
    "answer": "...'s wedding is probably up next"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who makes you laugh the hardest?",
    "answer": "... makes us laugh the hardest!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who should DJ every party?",
    "answer": "... should DJ every party"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to kill at an open mic?",
    "answer": "... is definitely going to kill at an open mic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is most likely to kill at an open mic?",
    "answer": "... is definitely going to kill at an open mic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Think about them way more than they know",
    "answer": "We think about ... way more than they know"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your ideal study buddy",
    "answer": "... is our ideal study buddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most creative",
    "answer": "... is the most creative"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most likely to be on SNL",
    "answer": "... is up on SNL next :D"
  },
  {
    "question": "Steals a free cookie on free cookie day",
    "answer": "... steals free cookies on free cookie day"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drops their phone in the toilet",
    "answer": "... drops their phone in the toilet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Best person to get coffee with",
    "answer": "... is the best person to get coffee with"
  },
  {
    "question": "Silliest joke teller",
    "answer": "... is the silliest joke teller"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most likely to star in a Netflix series",
    "answer": "... is going to be on Netflix soon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would hold the elevator for an old lady",
    "answer": "... would hold the elevator for an old lady"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would FaceTime for hours",
    "answer": "I'd facetime ... for hourse"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hotter than the sun",
    "answer": "... is hotter than the sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "Secretly think they’re cute",
    "answer": "... is secretly the cutest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Everyone’s darling",
    "answer": "... is everyone's darling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Always dressed to impress",
    "answer": "... is dressed to impress"
  },
  {
    "question": "Takes every Buzzfeed Quiz",
    "answer": "... takes every Buzzfeed Quiz"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most likely to be an astronaut",
    "answer": "... is most likely to be an astronaut"
  },
  {
    "question": "Drops their phone on their face",
    "answer": "... drops their phone on their face most"
  },
  {
    "question": "Instagram model",
    "answer": "... is an Instagram model"
  },
  {
    "question": "Everyone’s darling",
    "answer": "... is everyone's darling"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sleeps on Zoom classes",
    "answer": "... sleeps on Zoom classes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anime lover",
    "answer": "... is an anime lover"
  },
  {
    "question": "Could become a philosopher",
    "answer": "... is probably a philosopher"
  },
  {
    "question": "Says things nobody else says",
    "answer": "... says things nobody else says"
  },
  {
    "question": "Screams during every horror movie",
    "answer": "... screams during every horror movie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would hold the elevator for an old lady",
    "answer": "... would hold the elevator for an old lady"
  },
  {
    "question": "Knows all the lyrics to every Justin Bieber song",
    "answer": "... is a Belieber"
  }
]